Experience a revolutionary friendship over 45 years.
Cuba and the Cameraman is a documentary film directed by Jon Alpert.
This revealing portrait of Cuba follows the lives of Fidel Castro and three
Cuban families affected by his policies over the last four decades.
Self, played by Jon Alpert.
Self, played by Fidel Castro.
Self, played by Angél Borrego.
Self, played by Cristobal Borrego.
Self, played by Gregorio Borrego.
Self, played by Luis Amores.
Cuba and the Cameraman is a 2017 American documentary film
written, directed and co-produced by Jon Alpert.
The film is a Netflix Original and was first shown at the
74th Venice International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of cuba, dictatorship,
poverty, communism, passage of time.